ACCION International Records MS196
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Communications and External Affairs records, 1950 -- 2012; 1985 -- 2005; MS196.006; 62.7 Linear Feet; 238 Audiovisual Object(s); 365 Digital Object(s)
  - Reprints and publicity, 1960 -- 2011; MS196.006.004; 18.1 Linear Feet; 147 Audiovisual Object(s)
    - Citybank Partners: Summer, 1997; MS196.006.004.021.00116; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - El Cajon, CA, 1997; MS196.006.004.021.00117; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - BID Extra, 1997; MS196.006.004.021.00118; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Miami Herald, 1997; MS196.006.004.021.00119; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Boston Globe, 1997; MS196.006.004.021.00120; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Boston Globe, 1997; MS196.006.004.021.00121; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Albuquerque Business Times, 1997; MS196.006.004.021.00122; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Hispanic Business, 1997; MS196.006.004.021.00123; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Scientific American, 1997; MS196.006.004.021.00124; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Business Ethics, 1997; MS196.006.004.021.00125; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Profiles M. Chu, 1996; MS196.006.004.021.00126; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Boston Globe M Chu and Clients, 1996; MS196.006.004.021.00127; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Articles, 1996; MS196.006.004.021.00128; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Articles, 1997; MS196.006.004.021.00129; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Press Cov. Archives, 1998; MS196.006.004.021.00130; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Press Cov. Archives, 1999; MS196.006.004.021.00131; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Press Cov. Archives, 2000; MS196.006.004.021.00132; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 21)
    - Tapping Resources of Mexico's Economy, 1988; MS196.006.004.022.00001; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Four-in-One Complex A First in Calexico, 1989; MS196.006.004.022.00002; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - How to Make a Poor Country Rich, 1989; MS196.006.004.022.00003; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - The Right Path, 1989; MS196.006.004.022.00004; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Trickle Up Theory, 1989; MS196.006.004.022.00005; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - The Urban Edge, 1989; MS196.006.004.022.00006; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Crusaders for Peru, 1989; MS196.006.004.022.00007; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Loan Programs Assist Latin American Firms, 1989; MS196.006.004.022.00008; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Boston Herald Sox Loser off Field, Too, 1989; MS196.006.004.022.00009; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Capitalism with a Human Face, 1989; MS196.006.004.022.00010; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Sanford Business School Magazine Study Tour Report: T Minus Z and Counting, 1989; MS196.006.004.022.00011; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Panoscope - The Other Economy, 1989; MS196.006.004.022.00012; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - The Tico Times, 1989; MS196.006.004.022.00013; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - The Daily Record - Horatio Alger Lives in the 3W, 1989; MS196.006.004.022.00014; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Times of the Americas - An Informal Case Study, 1989; MS196.006.004.022.00015; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Middlesex News - The informal sector thrives in Colombia, 1989; MS196.006.004.022.00016; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - ACCION lends hope to poor in Latin America - The Jamaica Record, 1989; MS196.006.004.022.00017; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Austin American Statements, 1989; MS196.006.004.022.00018; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - The Seattle Times - Small businesses need debt relief, 1989; MS196.006.004.022.00019; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - The Times of the Americas - Displaced drug workers must have viable alternatives, 1989; MS196.006.004.022.00020; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - The Reporter - Stanford Business School, 1989; MS196.006.004.022.00021; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Middlesex News and the Berkshire Eagle, 1989; MS196.006.004.022.00022; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Churchwoman Women Entrepreneurs in Costa Rica, 1989; MS196.006.004.022.00023; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - The Gardner News - Entrepreneurs Thrive in Mexico, 1989; MS196.006.004.022.00024; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Fortune Third World loans that don't go sour, 1989; MS196.006.004.022.00025; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - The Christian Science Monitor - Bigger bang for loan bucks, 1989; MS196.006.004.022.00026; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - St. Louis Post Dispatch = Latin Americans are repaying these loans, 1989; MS196.006.004.022.00027; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - The Plain Dealer - Private loan firm helping Latin American underclass, 1989; MS196.006.004.022.00028; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - The Pittsburgh Press - Small loans go a long way, 1989; MS196.006.004.022.00029; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Grassroots Development - Rethinking the informal sector, 1989; MS196.006.004.022.00030; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Fortune, 1989; MS196.006.004.022.00031; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Seeds - Micro Enterprise in Santo Domingo, 1989; MS196.006.004.022.00032; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Presidential End Hunger Award, 1989; MS196.006.004.022.00033; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - The Times of the Americas, 1990; MS196.006.004.022.00034; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Philadelphia Inquirer, 1990; MS196.006.004.022.00035; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Tweye / Time Warner pub., 1990; MS196.006.004.022.00036; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - TWEYE, 1990; MS196.006.004.022.00037; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - The Toronto Star - Small loans fight third world poverty, 1990; MS196.006.004.022.00038; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - The Ashbury Park Press, 1990; MS196.006.004.022.00039; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Albuquerque Journal, 1990; MS196.006.004.022.00040; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - The International Economy "The Informal Sector", 1990; MS196.006.004.022.00041; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - The Chronicle of Philanthropy, 1990; MS196.006.004.022.00042; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - No Small Change for Bolivia's Poor Insight, 1990; MS196.006.004.022.00043; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - South Mag M.E. out of the shadows, 1990; MS196.006.004.022.00044; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - SEEDS - cartagena Solidarity, 1990; MS196.006.004.022.00045; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Entrepreneurial Manager's Newsletter, 1990; MS196.006.004.022.00046; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Boston Herald - Sox's Pena a man of ACCION, 1990; MS196.006.004.022.00047; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Providence Journal - Pena Sox, 1990; MS196.006.004.022.00048; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Lutheran Commentator - Credit given where credit is due, 1990; MS196.006.004.022.00049; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Patriot Ledger, 1990; MS196.006.004.022.00050; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - National Journal, 1990; MS196.006.004.022.00051; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - The Plain Dealer - Triumph above tragedy, 1990; MS196.006.004.022.00052; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - L.A. Studies Pave the way for LA by EDR, 1990; MS196.006.004.022.00053; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - New England Business, 1990; MS196.006.004.022.00054; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - New England Business, 1990; MS196.006.004.022.00055; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Pensions and Investment, 1990; MS196.006.004.022.00056; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Pensions and Investment, 1990; MS196.006.004.022.00057; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - New York Times - Paraguay: Aid for Sm. Entrep., 1990; MS196.006.004.022.00058; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Time Boosting Cottage Capitalism, 1990; MS196.006.004.022.00059; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Inc. Money Talks, 1990; MS196.006.004.022.00060; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - LA Daily News Vecinos Del Valle, 1990; MS196.006.004.022.00061; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - The Daily Progress, Charlottesville, VA, 1991; MS196.006.004.022.00062; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - The Daily Progress, VA, 1991; MS196.006.004.022.00063; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Washington Report - Council of Americas Winter/Spring, 1991; MS196.006.004.022.00064; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - St. Petersburg, 1991; MS196.006.004.022.00065; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Berlin Journal, 1991; MS196.006.004.022.00066; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Toronto Star - Loans help tiny 3rd world businesses thrive, 1991; MS196.006.004.022.00067; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Toronto Star, 1991; MS196.006.004.022.00068; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - World Monitor - Guatemala, 1991; MS196.006.004.022.00069; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - World Monitor, 1991; MS196.006.004.022.00070; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Washington Report - Spring, 1991; MS196.006.004.022.00071; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Capital Ideas - Spring, 1991; MS196.006.004.022.00072; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Washington Times, 1991; MS196.006.004.022.00073; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - World Watch, 1991; MS196.006.004.022.00074; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Newslink / Chem. Newsletter, 1991; MS196.006.004.022.00075; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Washington times, 1991; MS196.006.004.022.00076; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - La Prensa de San Antonio, 1991; MS196.006.004.022.00077; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Rancho Sante Fe Reivew, 1991; MS196.006.004.022.00078; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Vecinos del Valle Spanish, 1991; MS196.006.004.022.00079; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Forbes, 1991; MS196.006.004.022.00080; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Wall Street Journal, 1991; MS196.006.004.022.00081; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Time, 1991; MS196.006.004.022.00082; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - San Antonio Express / San Juan Star, 1991; MS196.006.004.022.00083; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Cape Codder, 1991; MS196.006.004.022.00084; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Impact, 1991; MS196.006.004.022.00085; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - The New York Times, 1991; MS196.006.004.022.00086; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - San Antonio Express, 1991; MS196.006.004.022.00087; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - La Prensa El Diario, 1991; MS196.006.004.022.00088; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - The Boston Globe, 1991; MS196.006.004.022.00089; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - El Norte (espanol), 1991; MS196.006.004.022.00090; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Latin Finance, 1991; MS196.006.004.022.00091; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Conjuntura, 1991; MS196.006.004.022.00092; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Providence Journal, 1991; MS196.006.004.022.00093; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Frontlines, 1991; MS196.006.004.022.00094; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Business Mexico, 1991; MS196.006.004.022.00095; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Churchwoman Women Entrepreneurs in Costa Rica, 1991; MS196.006.004.022.00096; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - UTNE Reader, 1991; MS196.006.004.022.00097; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - SOS Fall/Winter, 1991; MS196.006.004.022.00098; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Citibank Partners in Progress ACCION New York, 1991; MS196.006.004.022.00099; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - AEO ACCION's UA Expansion Plan, 1991; MS196.006.004.022.00100; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Boston Herald, 1993; MS196.006.004.022.00101; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Lost Angeles Times, 1993; MS196.006.004.022.00102; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Journal of Commerce, 1993; MS196.006.004.022.00103; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - The Washington Post, 1993; MS196.006.004.022.00104; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Mothers and Children, Summer, 1993; MS196.006.004.022.00105; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Coop America, Summer/Fall, 1993; MS196.006.004.022.00106; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Yuma Daily Sun, 1996; MS196.006.004.022.00107; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - American Way, 1993; MS196.006.004.022.00108; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Forbes, 1993; MS196.006.004.022.00109; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Businessweek/Enterprise, 1993; MS196.006.004.022.00110; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Fast Company, 1993; MS196.006.004.022.00111; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Boston Business Journal, 1993; MS196.006.004.022.00112; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Albuquerque Journal, 1993; MS196.006.004.022.00113; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - San Diego Union Tribune, 1994; MS196.006.004.022.00114; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - San Antonio Business Journal, 1994; MS196.006.004.022.00115; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - San Antonio Business Journal, 1994; MS196.006.004.022.00116; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Alimentos Procesados, 1994; MS196.006.004.022.00117; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Noticias, 1994; MS196.006.004.022.00118; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Businessweek, 1994; MS196.006.004.022.00119; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - San Antonio Express, 1994; MS196.006.004.022.00120; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - San Antonio Express News, 1994; MS196.006.004.022.00121; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Inc. Small Business Exchange, Summer, 1994; MS196.006.004.022.00122; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Albuquerque Journal, 1994; MS196.006.004.022.00123; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - The Wall Street Journal, 1994; MS196.006.004.022.00124; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - New York Times, 1994; MS196.006.004.022.00125; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - La Prensa de San Antonio, 1994; MS196.006.004.022.00126; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - San Antonio Express News, 1994; MS196.006.004.022.00127; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - San Antonio Express News, 1994; MS196.006.004.022.00128; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - NYNEX, 1994; MS196.006.004.022.00129; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - San Diego Business Journal, 1994; MS196.006.004.022.00130; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Journal of Commerce / Boston Globe, 1994; MS196.006.004.022.00131; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Albuquerque Journal, 1994; MS196.006.004.022.00132; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Boston Business Journal, 1994; MS196.006.004.022.00133; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - El Diario, 1994; MS196.006.004.022.00134; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - BusinessWeekly, 1994; MS196.006.004.022.00135; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Los Angeles Times, 1994; MS196.006.004.022.00136; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - The Washington Post, 1994; MS196.006.004.022.00137; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Chicago Tribune, 1994; MS196.006.004.022.00138; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - San Antonio Business Journal ACCION Texas, 1995; MS196.006.004.022.00139; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - La Prensa San Diego, 1995; MS196.006.004.022.00140; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - San Diego Daily Transcript, 1995; MS196.006.004.022.00141; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - J.P. Morgan Capital Ideas ACCION New York, 1995; MS196.006.004.022.00142; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Inc. Magazine, 1995; MS196.006.004.022.00143; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - San Diego Union Tribune, 1995; MS196.006.004.022.00144; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - San Antonio Bus. Journal, 1995; MS196.006.004.022.00145; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - National Geographic, 1995; MS196.006.004.022.00146; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Albuquerque Journal, 1995; MS196.006.004.022.00147; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Albuquerque Journal, 1995; MS196.006.004.022.00148; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Crain's Sm. Bus. Chicago, 1995; MS196.006.004.022.00149; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - San Antonio Express News / San Antonio Business Journal, 1995; MS196.006.004.022.00150; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - san Jose Mercury News, 1995; MS196.006.004.022.00151; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Miami Herald, 1995; MS196.006.004.022.00152; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Wall Street Journal ACCION mentioned in box only, 1995; MS196.006.004.022.00153; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - JP Morgan Capital Ideas ACCION NY, 1995; MS196.006.004.022.00154; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Crosslines, 1995; MS196.006.004.022.00155; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - New York Times ACCION NY, 1995; MS196.006.004.022.00156; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Dallas Morning News Beijing, 1995; MS196.006.004.022.00157; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Boston Journal Rosalind gorin w/ ACCION mention, 1995; MS196.006.004.022.00158; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - The Rotarian, 1995; MS196.006.004.022.00159; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Economic Development Abroad US/LA, 1995; MS196.006.004.022.00160; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Idaho Statements, 1995; MS196.006.004.022.00161; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Economic Development Abroad / Bolivia BancoSol, 1995; MS196.006.004.022.00162; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Economic Reform Today, 1995; MS196.006.004.022.00163; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - American Banker Delma Soto, AL, NY Clearninghouse Association, 1995; MS196.006.004.022.00164; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Income Opportunities, 1995; MS196.006.004.022.00165; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Albuquerque Tribune, 1995; MS196.006.004.022.00166; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Albuquerque Journal, 1995; MS196.006.004.022.00167; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Christian Science Monitor - Calvert CTI, 1995; MS196.006.004.022.00168; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - UTNE Reader, 1996; MS196.006.004.022.00169; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Chicago Tribune - Banco Sol, 1996; MS196.006.004.022.00170; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Seeds Magazine, 1996; MS196.006.004.022.00171; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - The Tab, 1996; MS196.006.004.022.00172; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Int'l Herald Tribune, 1996; MS196.006.004.022.00173; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - El Paso Times, 1996; MS196.006.004.022.00174; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Herald / Globe "Bravo ACCION", 1996; MS196.006.004.022.00175; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Monday Developments, 1996; MS196.006.004.022.00176; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Wall Street Journal, 1997; MS196.006.004.022.00177; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Journal of Commerce, 1997; MS196.006.004.022.00178; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Observer, 1997; MS196.006.004.022.00179; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - San Antonio ExpressNews, 1997; MS196.006.004.022.00180; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - San Antonio Express News, 1997; MS196.006.004.022.00181; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - The Economist, 1997; MS196.006.004.022.00182; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - New Mexico Business Journal, 1997; MS196.006.004.022.00183; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Across the Board, 1997; MS196.006.004.022.00184; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - The Dallas Morning News, 1997; MS196.006.004.022.00185; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Lake Charles American, 1997; MS196.006.004.022.00186; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Gainesville Sun, 1997; MS196.006.004.022.00187; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Daily News Record, 1997; MS196.006.004.022.00188; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Hawaii Tribune Herald, 1997; MS196.006.004.022.00189; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Daily Commercial, 1997; MS196.006.004.022.00190; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Sun, 1997; MS196.006.004.022.00191; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Christian Science Monitor, 1997; MS196.006.004.022.00192; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Chronicle of Philanthropy, 1997; MS196.006.004.022.00193; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Albuquerque Tribune, 1997; MS196.006.004.022.00194; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Journal of Commerce, 1997; MS196.006.004.022.00195; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - The Sun, 1997; MS196.006.004.022.00196; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - Monday Developments, 1997; MS196.006.004.022.00197; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - The Arizona Daily Star, 1997; MS196.006.004.022.00198; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)
    - The Earth Times, 1997; MS196.006.004.022.00199; ACCION International (Organization) (Box 22)